Guide to the Yale University Divinity School Memorabilia Collection
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Life at YDS, Series III
  - Chronological file
    - 1900-1955
      - Notes on the announcement and dedication of SDQ, 1931 May 4, 1932 Oct 3 (Box III-2)
      - Annual Reports; Articles; Speeches, 1932 (Box III-2)
      - Articles and Programs, 1933 (Box III-2)
      - Department of Field Work - Annual reports, news statements, 1934 (Box III-2)
      - 113th Anniversary; Case of Jerome Davis, 1935-1936 (Box III-2)
      - Dwight Hall, 1936 (Box III-2)
      - 236th Commencement of Yale University; American Association of Professors; Vespers service, 1937 (Box III-2)
      - Yale Christian Association, 1937 (Box III-2)
      - Lyman Beecher Lectures, 1937 (Box III-2)
      - Code of Ethics - Field Placement; Students' Religious Preferences, 1938 (Box III-2)
      - 117th Anniversary; 50th Year of Charles Brown's Ordination; Opening service; Convocation; Christian Conference, 1939 (Box III-2)
      - 239th Commencement - Yale; Correspondence; Convocation; 118th Anniversary of YDS, 1940 (Box III-2)
      - Correspondence Concerning the War, 1940-1945 (Box III-2)
      - "Lux et Veritas"; 119th Anniversary; "Co-op Report", 1941 (Box III-2)
      - "What Every Young Minister Ought to Know"; Programs, 1942 (Box III-2)
      - Newspaper Clippings; Chapel Programs; Correspondence, 1944 (Box III-2)
      - Joint Committee on Graduate and Professional School Alumni (luncheon meeting), 1944 May 20 (Box III-2)
      - Curriculum Report; Articles; Graduation Exercises, 1945 (Box III-2)
      - Divinity School Timetable; Yale Hope Mission; Articles, 1947 (Box III-2)
      - Yale Divinity School Catalogue; Foreign Mission Library and Two Hundredth Anniversary of Yale College, 1900-1902 (Box III-2)
      - "New Directions for Religion in Higher Education"; Calendar, 1948 (Box III-2)
      - Dormitory rules; Opening service; Orientation program, Field work information; Student Book Supply; Library use rules, 1948 (Box III-2)
      - Choir report; Calendar; Denominational preferences; Articles, 1949 (Box III-2)
      - Opening service; Orientation; Address list; Field work, 1949 (Box III-2)
      - Orientation materials, 1949 (Box III-2)
      - Curriculum Committee, 1949-1965 (Box III-2)
      - Anniversary Exercises; Dean's Report (Liston Pope), 1950 (Box III-2)
      - Opening service and events, 1950 (Box III-2)
      - Convocation Announcements, 1950-1955 (Box III-2)
      - Student Book Supply, 1950-1951 (Box III-2)
      - 215th Anniversary of Yale; Correspondence; Dean's Report, 1951 (Box III-2)
      - Alumni Fund Campaign; Entering Students; Correspondence, 1952 (Box III-2)
      - 132nd Year - Opening services; Orientation program, 1953 (Box III-2)
      - Report of the Divinity School, 1952-1954; Articles (Box III-2)
      - Articles concerning Yale Divinity School, 1955 (Box III-2)
    - 1956-1969
      - "Theological Education in America"; Architectural plans, 1956 (Box III-3)
      - Convocation Announcements, 1956-1959 (Box III-3)
      - Dedication of the New Buildings; Correspondence, 1957 (Box III-3)
      - Vignettes of Men Memorialized in the Buildings of the Yale Divinity School, by Roland Bainton, [1957] (Box III-3)
      - Dean's Report; Faculty Meeting Minutes; Correspondence, 1958 (Box III-3)
      - Board Meeting Minutes; Faculty Meeting Minutes, 1959 (Box III-3)
      - Committee on Scholarly Publications, 1959-1964 (Box III-3)
      - Fellowship of Southern Churchmen at YDS, 1960 (Box III-3)
      - Faculty Meeting Minutes; Correspondence, 1960 (Box III-3)
      - 260th Commencement; Faculty Meeting Minutes, 1961 (Box III-3)
      - Acting Dean's Report (Charles Forman); Faculty Minutes, 1962 (Box III-3)
      - Administrative Reports, Committees, 1962 (Box III-3)
      - Committee on the Appointment of a Dean, 1962 Jan-Jul (Box III-3)
      - Committee on the Appointment of a Dean, 1962 Aug-Dec (Box III-3)
      - Committee on the Appointment of a Dean, 1963 Jan-Mar, n.d. (Box III-3)
      - Committee on Faculty, 1962-1966 (Box III-3)
      - Memorial Service; Minutes From Officers; 262nd Commencement, 1963 (Box III-3)
      - Student Religious Organizations and Activities, 1963-1968 (Box III-3)
      - Faculty Meeting MInutes, 1964 (Box III-3)
      - Committee on Development, 1964-1970 (Box III-3)
      - Committee on Portraits, 1965 (Box III-3)
      - 265th Commencement; Student Information, 1966 (Box III-3)
      - Committee on Professional Studies, 1966-1967, n.d. (Box III-3)
      - Registration Procedure; Correspondence, 1967 (Box III-3)
      - Committee on Faculty, 1967-1969 (Box III-3)
      - Self Study, 1967-1968 (Box III-3)
      - Faculty Meeting Minutes; Election Poll; Correspondence, 1968 (Box III-3)
      - The Draft Law, 1969 (Box III-3)
      - Yale University and Social Unrest, 1969 (Box III-3)
    - 1970-1999
      - Committee on Publications, 1969-1970 (Box III-4)
      - Articles in N.H. Register about YDS by John Knoble, 1970s (Box III-4)
      - Articles; Faculty Meeting Minutes, 1970 (Box III-4)
      - Administrative Reports, Committees, 1970-1971 (Box III-4)
      - Articles; Faculty Correspondence; 270th Commencement, 1971 (Box III-4)
      - Convocation Announcements, 1970-1999 (Box III-4)
      - Core Groups, 1971-1972 (Box III-4)
      - Ecumenical Continuing Education, 1971 (Box III-4)
      - Correspondence; Articles; Programs, 1972 (Box III-4)
      - Class Schedule; Institute of Sacred Music, 1973 (Box III-4)
      - Questionnaire Result; Berkeley Evaluation; Handbook, 1974 (Box III-4)
      - Yale Campaign, 1975 (Box III-4)
      - Articles Concerning YDS, 1976-1978 (Box III-4)
      - "Tenth Anniversary of Yale - Berkeley Affiliation", 1979-1981 (Box III-4)
      - Articles in N.H. Register about YDS by John Knoble, 1980s (Box III-4)
      - Union Correspondence; Opening of Renovated Libraries, 1982-1984 (Box III-4)
      - Jerusalem Symposium: Religion and the Arts, 1983 (Box OV-Drawer 1)
      - Report to University Budget Committee, 1985 (Box III-4)
      - Baccalaureate Service, 1986 (Box III-4)
      - Opening Convocation; Library Guide; Baccalaureate, 1987 (Box III-4)
      - Administrative Reports, Committees, 1987-1988 (Box III-4)
      - Baccalaureate Service; LIbrary News, 1988 (Box III-4)
      - Articles; State of the School Report; Baccalaureate; Opening Convocation, 1989-1990 (Box III-4)
      - Commencement Service; Supervised Ministries Report, YDS Student Directory, 1991-1992 (Box III-4)
      - Building Divinity, by John W. Cook (history of SDQ), 1994 (Box III-4)
      - Yale Studies in Sacred Music, 1994-1995 (Box III-4)
      - Spring Course Syllabus, 1995 (Box III-4)
      - Orientation; Announcement of New Dean; Correspondence; Newspaper clippings, 1995-1996 (Box III-4)
      - Divinity School Review Committee, 1995-1996 (Box III-4)
      - "The Future of Divinity" in Yale Alumni Magazine, 1996 Mar (Box III-4)
      - Class schedule, 1996 Fall (Box III-4)
      - Faculty meeting minutes; Baccalaureate and Commencement programs; Reunion; Colloquium on The Will (1996), 1996-1998 (Box III-4)
      - Racism Workshop, 1997 (Box III-4)
      - Lutheran Studies Program, 1997 (Box III-4)
      - Advent Vespers, 1998-1999 (Box III-4)
      - Community Lunch, 1999 (Box III-4)
      - Sterling Bequest: Appellate Court of Connecticut, Cynthia Sterling Russell v. Yale University; decided 1999 Aug 24 (Box III-4)
    - 2000-present
      - Convocation Announcements (Box III-5)
      - Hartford Seminary: Cooperative Program with YDS, 2000 (Box III-5)
      - Worship, 2000-2003 (Box III-5)
      - The Revitalization of the Sterling Divinity Quadrangle; Newspaper Clippings, 2001,2002, 2003 (Box III-5)
      - YDS Orientation Schedule, 2002 (Box III-5)
      - Chapel Renovations Proposal, 2003 May (Box III-5)
      - Traditional Building, "The Revitalization of the Sterling Divinity Quadrangle", 2004 (Box III-5)
      - YDS Student Autobiographies, 2004, 2006 (Box III-5)
      - Memorial Program for Letty Mandeville Russell (1929-2007), 2007 Jul 28 (Box III-5)
      - YDS Alumni Awards Dinner, Woolsey Hall, 2015 Oct 22 (Box III-5)
  - Subject file
    - Administrative Reports and Committees (Box III-6)
    - YDS Association, n.d. (Box III-6)
    - ASPEN, n.d. (Box III-6)
    - Black Presence at YDS, n.d. (Box III-6)
    - Campus Life, n.d. (Box III-6)
    - Center for Faith and Culture, 2003-2004, 2006 (Box III-6)
    - Christian Activity at Yale, n.d. (Box III-6)
    - Coffin-Forsberg Fellows, 1998–1999 (Box III-6)
    - Conferences, 2000 Feb 4-6, n.d.; 1 (Box III-6)
      including YDS All-School Conference on Dialogue and Conference on Future of Ecumenism
    - Constitution, YDS Association, n.d. (Box III-6)
    - Curriculum Committee, 1949–1965 (Box III-6)
    - Ecumenical Continuation Education Center at Yale, 1971 (Box III-6)
    - Educational Leadership Ministry Program (ELM), 2010–2011 (Box III-6)
    - Faculty Wives (Box III-6)
    - Farm at YDS, 2010- (Box III-6)
    - Guest Register, n.d. (Box III-6)
    - Initiative on Religion and Politics, 2006 (Box III-6)
    - The In-Parish Pastoral Studies Program (4 folders), n.d. (Box III-6)
    - Keck Communication Program dedication, 1991 Oct 9 (Box III-6)
    - Lay School of Religion, 1978 (Box III-6)
    - Lutheran Studies Program, 1997- (Box III-6)
    - Martin Luther King, Jr. Visit to Yale YDS., 1959 Jan 14-15 (Box III-6)
    - Open Party (sponsor of Taylor House Lectures), 2012-1014 (Box III-6)
    - PEW Program in Religion American History, 1977 (Box III-6)
    - YDS Requirements, n.d. (Box III-6)
    - Rules of the Divinity School of Yale University, n.d. (Box III-6)
    - Scholarship funds (Box III-6)
    - South Africa divestment efforts, 1978 (Box III-6)
    - Special Events; Worship, n.d. (Box III-6)
    - Sterling Memorial Library holding related to YDS (photocopied catalog cards) (Box III-6)
    - Student Book Supply, 1950-1951 (Box III-6)
    - Student Religious Organizations Activities, 1886, 1911-1957; 1963-68, 2014, n.d. (Box III-6)
    - War efforts, 1940-1945 (Box III-6)
    - War: Ministry in Time of War: YDS and WWII - papers, news clippings, brochures, 1940-1945 (Box III-6)
    - Wesley Foundation at Yale (Box III-6)
    - "Window Shopping with the Divinity Doubles", ed. by Fran and James Dittes (Box III-6)
    - Works of Jonathan Edwards (Box III-6)
    - Worship, n.d. (Box III-6)
    - Yale Committee on Social Ministry, 1992 (Box III-6)
- YDS Publications and Lectures, 1822-present; Series IV
  - Major serial publications
    - General Catalogue, 1822-1922 (Box IV-1)
    - Bulletin, 1856-1959 (Box IV-2)
      Existence and Location of Copies
      (NB: Microfilm (positive) of issues for 1862/63, 1866/67, 1869/70-1977/79. New Haven, Conn.; Yale University Photographic Services, 1984. 5 microfilm reels; 35 mm.)
    - Bulletin, 1960-present; 1 (Box IV-3)
    - Student Handbooks, 1981/82, 1991/92-2000/01, 2005/06; 0.5 (Box IV-4)
    - Student Directories, 1950-1999; 1 (Box IV-5)
    - Student Directories, 2000-present; 0.5 (Box IV-6)
    - Faculty/Staff Directories, 1958- present; 0.5 (Box IV-7)
    - Dial (Continued by "Q-Source"), 1951-1984; 1 (Box IV8)
    - Dial (Continued by "Q-Source"), 1992-1995; 0.5 (Box IV-9)
    - Q-Source, 1995-2009; 1 (Box IV-10A)
    - Q-Source, Dear Theo, 2010-present; 1983-1984, 1988, 1991-1994, 1995-1997, 2005-; 0.5 (Box IV-10B)
    - Yale Divinity Quarterly (Continued by Yale Divinity News), 1904-1920; 0.5 (Box IV-11)
    - Yale Divinity News (Continued by Reflection), 1920-1965; 1 (Box IV-12)
    - Reflection, 1965-present; 1 (Box IV-13)
    - Spectrum, 1987-present; 1 (Box IV-14)
    - Signs Times, 1960-1965; 0.5 (Box IV-15)
    - Dear Theo, 1983-1984, 1988, 1991-1994, 1995-1997, 2005, 2012; 7 (Box IV-10)
    - Taylor House lectures* (see Open Party) (Box IV-10)
    - Commencement/Baccalaureate Programs, 1992-present; 1 (Box IV-16)
  - Miscellaneous publications
    - Admissions brochures, booklets, 1990s (Box IV-17)
    - Arts Festival publications (Box IV-17)
    - Bicentennial of Yale (Yale Alumni Weekly), 1902 (Box IV-17)
    - Building Divinity, by John W. Cook (history of SDQ), 1994 (Box IV-17)
    - "YDS Catholic Presence", 1994-96 (Box IV-17)
    - Distanced from Divinity: the 1932 re-housing of Yale Divinity School, by Larry Gipson, [2011] (Box IV-17)
    - The Yale Divinity School before its move to 409 Prospect Street: from a History of Yale College, published in 1879 / edited and introduced by Allison Stokes (on the occasion of YDS's 190th year). Published/Created:[New Haven, Conn.: Yale Divinity School, 2012] (Box IV-17)
    - "The Diviner", 2002-2004 (Box IV-17)
    - Centenary of Yale Divinity School, Alumni Weekly, 1922 Oct 20 (Box IV-17)
    - Centennial issue, 1822-1888 1888-1902 1822-1922 (Box IV-17)
    - "Eschatology Today", 1977-1978 (Box IV-17)
    - Fiat Lux: Yale student journal of religion, 2009 (Box IV-17)
    - "Friends of Edwards", 1953-1959 (Box IV-17)
    - Historical Buildings of YDS, 2015 (Box IV-17)
    - Hymnal (published by YDS), 1952 (Box IV-17)
    - "In Context", 1953-1959 (Box IV-17)
    - "Laudamus: Services and Songs of Praise", 1980 (Box IV-17)
    - "The Limb", 1965-1970 (Box IV-17)
    - Miscellaneous Reports, 1930-31, 1963-73, 1975 (Box IV-17)
    - "Nota Bene" - publication correspondence, notes, drafts, 1988-1990 (Box IV-17)
    - Obituary Record of Record of Graduates of Yale Colllege: who have died during the academical year 1859-60, including the names of ... who died the year previous, hitherto unreported [Nos 1-10 of the First Printed Series], 1860-1869 (Box IV-10)
    - Prospect. "A journal of poetry, fiction and art produced by a few students at Yale Divinity School, New Haven.", 2006- (Box IV-17)
    - Renovating the Yale Divinity School Campus: a brief overview, by James M. Phillips, Rev. ed. 2004 (Box IV-17)
    - "The Root", 1971 (Box IV-17)
    - Shibboleth, 1981 (Box IV-17)
    - "Student Weekly", 1938-1940 (Box IV-17)
    - "University Divinity Schools: A Report on Ecclesiastically Independent Theological Education" - George Lindbeck, 1976 (Box IV-17)
    - Update: Yale Divinity School, Berkeley Divinity School, Institute of Sacred Music., 1998-2000 (Box IV-17)
    - "The Wellspring", 1947 (Box IV-17)
    - "The Yale Epistle", 1952-1954 (Box IV-17)
    - Update: Yale Divinity School, Berkeley Divinity School, Institute of Sacred Music. (Box IV-17)
    - View from 490 Prospect Street, by Joan Delaney, OMSC, 1998 (Box IV-17)
    - Vignettes of Men Memorialized in the Buildings of YDS, by Roland Bainton, 1957; reprint 1989/1990 (Box IV-17)
    - Voice (publication of YDS Women's Center), 2000,2002 (Box IV-17)
    - YDS Broadside, 1982 (Box IV-10)
    - Yale Daily News (selected issues), 1915-1917, 1921-1923, 1977 (Box IV-10)
    - "YDS News" - Social Action Committee, 1948 (Box IV-10)
    - Yale Weekly Bulletin (selected issues), 1978 Jul; 1990 Oct (Box IV-10)
    - The Yale Standard, 1969 (Box IV-10)
  - Lecture series, The material regarding Named Lecture Series is general in nature; text of the lectures is not available in this series, though may be available in published form or on audio recordings. The files contain correspondence between the Dean of YDS and the lecturers, including letters of invitation to present lectures and letters of appreciation for having lectured. Some files include CVs on the lecturers and other information pertinent to the topic of the lectures.
    See also: Series 5, Audio-Visual Materials
    - General (2 folders) (Box IV-18)
      Information about Yale named lectures
    - Roland Bainton Lectures (16 folders), 1987/88-2004/05 (Box IV-18)
      2004-2005 Andrew F. Walls (11/16/04) 2003-2004 H. C. Eric Midelfort (4/1/04) 2002-2003 Gary Wills (declined) -10/2002 2001-2002 Lamin Sanneh (10/1/02) 2000-2001 Barbara Newman (10/10/00) 1998-1999 Frank M. Tumer (10/12/98) 1996-1997 Albert Raboteau (10/16/97) 1995-1996 Margaret R. Miles (10/10/95) 1994-1995 Robert Bellah (2/7/95) 1993-1994 E. Glenn Hinson (11/3/93) 1992-1993 John Howard Yoder(declined)-4/1993 1991-1992 Beyers Naude (declined) - 2/1993 1990-1991 Clarissa W. Atkinson (2/5/91) 1989-1990 James Washington (2/13/90) 1988-1989 Donald G Mathews (2/15/89) 1987-1988 Eric W Gritsch (2/16/88)
    - Bartlett Lectures (17 folders), 1987/88-2004/05 (Box IV-18)
      2004-2005 Diane B. Obenchain (11/9/04) 2003-2004 Daniel Bays (2/19/04) 2002-2003 Barbara Brown Zikmund (9/9/03) 2000-2001 Emily Townes (10/12/00) 1999-2000 Larry Minear (declined) - 2/1999 1997-1998 Harold Koh (10/16/97) 1996-1997 Robert Burt (10/9/96) 1995-1996 Usa Sowle Cahill (10/11/95) 1994-1995 David Uttle (2/7/95) 1994-1995 Cornell West (declined) - 2/1995 1992-1993 Nathan O. Hatch (2/9/93) 1991-1992 Michael McGiffert (2/11/92) 1990-1991 Franklin J. Woo (2/6/91) 1990-1991 Bishop K. H. Ting (declined) - 2/1991 1989-1990 Robert T. Handy (2/14/90) 1988-1989 David M. Stowe (4/13/89) 1987-1988 Martin E. Marty (1213/87)
    - Lyman Beecher Lectures (48 folders), 1996/97-2004-05 (Box IV-18)
      2004-2005 Otis Moss, Jr. (10/9-15/04) 2003-2004 Ellen F. Davis (10/11-17/03) 2002-2003 J. Barrie Shepherd (10/12-17/02) 2001-2002 David L Bartlett (10/1-4/01) 2000-2001 Barbara Lundblad (10/7-13/00) 1999-2000 Richard Alan Lischer (10/10-14/99) 1998-1999 Peter J. Gomes (10/10-14/98) 1997-1998 Barbara Brown Taylor (10/12-16/97) 1996-1997 David G. Buttrick (10/6-9/96) 1995-1996 Harry B. Adams (10/9-12/95) 1994-1995 Peggy Brainard Way (2/6-9/94) 1993-1994 Walter Burghardt (2/7-10/94) 1992-1993 Thomas J. Hoyt, Jr. (2/19-11/93) 1991-1992 Leander Keck (2/10-12/92) 1990-1991 Bartlett, Childs, Farley, Malherbe (2/5-7/91) 1989-1990 Samuel D. Proctor (2/12-16/90) 1988-1989 Walter Brueggmann (2/12-16/89) 1987 -1988 John B. Coburn (2/8-11/88) 1986-1987 Horace T. Allen, Jr. (2/9-12/87) 1974-1975 Davie Napier (2/18-20/75) 1972-1973 David H. C. Read (4/24-26/73) 1970-1971 Multi-media presentation 1969-1970 Ivan D. lllich (2/16-18/70) 1968-1969 Paul Ramsey (4/14-17/69) 1967-1968 Paul W. Pruyser (4/68) 1966-1967 Sidney E. Mead (4/25-27/67) 1965-1966 Lesslie Newbigin (4/26-28/66) 1964-1965 Jackson Burns (4/27 -29/65) 1963-1964 Daniel Jenkins (4/14-16/64) 1962-1963 Herbert Gezork (declined) 4/1963 1962-1963 Browne Barr (4/16-18/63) 1961-1962 Samuel H. Miller (4/24-26/62) 1960-1961 Gene E. Bartlett (4/4-6/61) 1959-1960 Donald O. Soper 4/19-21/60) 1958-1959 Joseph Sitler (3/31/59-4/2/59) 1957-1958 Douglas Horton 4/8-10/58) 1956-1957 Daniel T. Niles (4/23-25/57) 1955-1956 Angus Dun (4/3-5/56) 1954-1955 James H. Robinson (4/12-14/55) 1953-1954 Gerald Kennedy (4/20-22/54) 1952-1953 Halford E. Luccock (4/7-9/53) 1951-1952 James S. Stewart (4/15-17/52) 1950-1951 Truman B. Douglas (6/6-8/51) 1949-1950 H. M. Wriston, A. S. Flemming, W. H. Auden, E. W. Sinnott, H. Kenyon (4/18-20/50)
    - Chisholm Lectures (4 folders), 2000/01-2005/06 (ceased) (Box IV-18)
      2005-2006 Susan Ackerman (1/31/06) 2004-2005 Baruch Levin (10/26/04) 2002-2003 John Barton (3/27/03) 2000-2001 Carol Newsom (10/10/00)
    - Ensign Lectures (10 folders), 1995/96-2004/05 (Box IV-19)
      2004-2005 Don Cupitt (2/28/05) 2003-2004 Nancy Ammerman (10/14/03) 2002-2003 Avery Cardinal Dulles (9/23/03) 2001-2002 Margaret Farley (10/4/01) 2000-2001 Marie M. Fortune (10/13/00) 1999-2000 William Julius Wilson (declined) -10/1993 1998-1999 Jean B. Ehlstain (10/15/98) 1997-1998 Sr. Helen Prejan (10/15/97) 1996-1997 Mercy Amba Oduyoye (10/7/96) 1995-1996 William F. May (10/9/95)
    - Hoskins Lectures (5 folders), 1985/86-2006/07 (Box IV-19)
      2004-2005-2006-2007 Rev. Warren H. Stewart (4/9-12/07) 1991-1992 J. Alfred Smith (4/8-10/92) 1989-1990 Jim Wallis (4/4-6/90) 1987 -1988 Mary Lee Daugherty (11/2-4/87) 1985-1986 Marie M. Fortune (10/28-30/85)
    - Kittel Lectures (8 folders), 1984/85-1993/94 (ceased) (Box IV-19)
      1993-1994 Susan Niditch (4/20/94) 1991-1992 Carol Newsome (10/16/91) 1990-1991 Patrick Miller (10/17/90) 1989-1990 Walter Harrelson (10/18/89) 1988-1989 Jon D. Levenson (2/22/89) 1987-1988 Elizabeth Achtemeier (10/13/87) 1986-1987 Norman Gottwald (9/29/86) 1984-1985 David Freedman (10/22/84)
    - Luccock Lectures (5 folders), 1986/87-2002/03 (Box IV-19)
      2002-2003 Timothy Hickey (11/5-7/02) 2001-2002 William D. Campbell (declined) 3/2001 1992-1993 Jeremiah A. Wright, Jr. (4/13-15/93) 1988-1989 Joseph L. Roberts, Jr. (4/5-7/89) 1986-1987 Joan M. Martin (3/30-4/1/87)
    - Parks-King Lectures (10 folders), 1990/91-2004/05 (Box IV-19)
      2004-2005 John Kinney (2/15/05) 2003-2004 Robert Franklin (2/26/04) 2001-2002 Barbara Holmes (2/28/02) 2000-2001 Peter Paris (3/1/01) 1998-1999 Renita Weems (2/5/99) 1997-1998 Kelly Brown Douglas (4/7/98) 1994-1995 Barbara Rose Collins (3/24/95) 1994-1995 Rosa Parks (no correspondence) 1993-1994 Peter Paris (3/24/94) 1990-1991 Calvin Butts (2/91)
    - Shaffer Lectures (29 folders), 1949/50-2002/03 (Box IV-19)
      2002-2003 Susan Garrett (10/15-17/02) 2000-2001 J. Louis Martyn (10/10-12/00) 1998-1999 Abraham J. Malherbe (10/13-15/98) 1996-1997 Nicholas Thomas Wright (10/7-9/96) 1994-1995 Morna Hooker (2/7 -8/95) 1992-1993 Martin Hengel (2/8-11/93) 1990-1991 Ed P. Sanders (2/4-7/91) 1988-1989 Marinus R. de Jonge (2/14-16/89) 1986-1987 Elizabeth Schussler Fiorenza (2/87) 1971-1972 James Sanders (4/18-19/72) 1969-1970 James Robinson 1968-1969 W. D. Davies (11/12-14/68) 1966-1967 Krister Stendahl (4/25-27/67) 1965-1966 Ernst Kasemann (4/26-28/66) 1964-1965 C. K. Barrett (4/27-29/65) 1962-1963 Gunther Bornkamm (3/11-14/63) 1961-1962 Nils A. Dahl (4/24-26/62) 1960-1961 William Cornelis van Unnik (4/24-27/61) 1959-1960 Erich Dinkler (11/2-5/59) 1958-1959 Frederick Grant (2/23-26/59) 1957-1958 Gerhard von Rad (declined) 4/1959 1955-1956 John Knox (2/13-16/56) 1953-1954 Amos Wilder (4/20-22/54) 1951-1952 Luther A. Weigle (9/30-10/3/52) 1951-1952 Karl Barth (declined) 1951-1952 Richard Livingstone (declined) 1951-1952 Dorothy L Sayers (declined) 1950-1951 Rudolf Bultmann (10/15-18/51) 1949-1950 Robert H. McCracken (4/18-20/50)
    - Margaret Lindquist Sorensen Lectures (25 folders), 1984/85-2004/05 (Box IV-19)
      2004-2005 Don Cupitt, Richard Mollica (2/28-3/1/05) 2004-2005 Thomas Berry (declined) 2003-2004 Charles E. Curran (10/13/03) 2002-2003 Ronald J. Sider (10/15/02) 2000-2001 Stanley Hauerwas (10/9/00) 1999-2000 Delores Williams (10/11/99) 1998-1999 Kurt Schmoke (4/8/99) 1997-1998 James Childress (10/16/97) 1996-1997 The Honorable James T. Laney (3/26/97) 1995-1996 Albert Gore (declined) 1995-1996 Marian Wright Edelman (no response) 1994-1995 James M. Gustafson (2/6/95) 1993-1994 Richard John Neuhaus (3/28/94) 1992-1993 Guido Calabresi (4/1/93) 1991-1992 Beverly Harrison (4/1/92) 1990-1991 George McGovern (4/29/91) 1989-1990 David Price (2/13/90) 1988-1989 Robin W. Lovin (10/13/88) 1987-1988 William Lee Miller (4/6/88) 1986-1987 John C. Danforth (10/24/86) 1985-1986 David Hollenbach (10/17/85) 1984-1985 Sheldon Wolin, Sr. Augusta Neal, Brian Hehir (10/8/84)
    - Nathaniel Taylor Lectures (34 folders), 1950/51-2003/04 (Box IV-19)